<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on haimantika</title>
    <link>https://haimantika.github.io/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on haimantika</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://haimantika.github.io/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DevRelCon Yokohama 2023</title>
      <link>https://haimantika.github.io/articles/devblogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haimantika.github.io/articles/devblogs/</guid>
      <description>DevRelCon Yokohama was all about meeting amazing people, a lot of learnings, some &amp;ldquo;this is my first time doing it&amp;rdquo; and a lot of FUN!
This was my first time speaking in a in-person international conference, I was excited and nervous at the same time. It was a two day conference, happening in Yokohama, Japan. I have been friends with the DevRelCon Tokyo/Yokohama organising team since 2020, I was a speaker for the online edition (also a major reason why I chose my career in DevRel).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Subtle Art Of Cold Emailing</title>
      <link>https://haimantika.github.io/articles/article2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haimantika.github.io/articles/article2/</guid>
      <description>What is cold- emailing? Is there a dream company/dream role you want to work for? Do you want a reply from your favorite celebrity? Do you want to get mentored by your idol? Cold-emailing can do it for you!
You never know, when a simple tweet or an email or a message can lead to your first big hit! Put your creative hat on and get the desired results!
There are numerous examples of people getting hired from a LinkedIn post or an email, becoming a social media celebrity overnight and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome 👋</title>
      <link>https://haimantika.github.io/articles/article/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haimantika.github.io/articles/article/</guid>
      <description>Hi 👋 Haimantika here! We finally have a portfolio, where you get to find everything about me in one place.
For those who are new here, hi! I am Haimantika, a Developer Advocate at Appwrite and used to work at Microsoft for a short stint as a Support Engineer.
I come from a small city, Siliguri located in the North Eastern part of India. Fun fact - I never wanted to do engineering, fast forward to 6 years, now I have an engineering degree and working full-time in tech for 2 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is DevRel?</title>
      <link>https://haimantika.github.io/articles/article1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haimantika.github.io/articles/article1/</guid>
      <description>DevRels are making the heads turn and if you think it&amp;rsquo;s because the job is cool, you are mistaken. It is because the term is relatively new and many are unaware of the role.
If I had to express that in a tweet, it would go something like 👇 {% embed https://twitter.com/HaimantikaM/status/1600488249205850114?s=20&amp;amp;t=LJ8zgc0NBxwuuchIfb_bWg %}
P.S - The definition of DevRel has a lot to do with individual perspectives and company goals. In this article I will try to put a generalised view of the role.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
